OFIR ADATO

QA + AUTOMATION TESTER

ofiradatowork@gmail.com OfirAdato

J 050-9464923

Holon, Israel

in HTTPS://www.linkedin.com/in/ofir-adato/

ABOUT ME

Quality assurance and automation tester, understands and loves the world of testing, Theoretical as well as practical, including writing STP, STD, STR test documents. Practical experience in the testing processes including test management in Test Rail, Jira, Visual Studio bug reports and STR release. Understanding and experience working with CSS, HTML, java and selenium.

Understanding of work processes (Agile, water fall).

WORK EXPERIENCE

* OCT' 23 -MAY 24 Recruited to unit 376 in the Signal corps.

QA Tester

'CALL-FLOW SOFTWARE'

- January 2023 September 2023 ▼ Tel-Aviv
- Responsible for writing and executing STPs for new features.
- Manual testing according to existing STPs.
- Creating STRs using visual studio.
- Responsible for complex SQL queries used to customize tests.

Level B Technician

'ONE-TALDOR'

- **April** 2021 January 2023
- Petah Tigwa
- A level B technician of ATM machines.
- Technician of computer hardware.

Field Service Technician

- 'BRINKS'
- **Dec 2019 April 2021**
- ▼ Tel-Aviv
- Technician of ATM machine.

MILITARY SERVICE

Signal Corps

MAR 2017 - NOV 2019

Commanders course

- **2018**
- I served as a company sergeant and managed everything related to work arrangements, company tasks.
- Operation of faults in CISCO and JUNIPER routers and switches.

PROJECTS

Project 1

https://ofiradato.github.io/Ofir-website/

• My profile website

CERTIFICATIONS

Quality assurance - Tester
"QA MASTERS"

i June 2022 -October 2022

Automation - Tester
"QA MASTERS"

October 2022 - February 2023

SKILLS

SQL HTML CSS JAVA

Selenium | TestNG | Pag

PageFactory

SOFT SKILLS

Team Work Problem-Solving Responsibility

Self-Learning Strategic Thinking Flexibility

Hard-working Eye for detail

Motivator & Leader

LANGUAGES

EDUCATION

"QA MASTERS"

JUNE 2022 - OCTOBER 2022

Thesis title: QA TESTER

"QA MASTERS"

October 2022 - February 2023

Thesis title: AUTOMATION TESTER